- Fry! That's disgusting!
- What?
You double-dipped! Geez.
Crew, you're working too hard.
Tell me about it.
For once, I thought it might be nice
to do something in a social setting,
finally get to know each other.
Why, I don't even know half your names!
You, boy. What do they call you?
Most folks just call me Orange Joe.
So, Professor, where are we gonna go?
It's July, right?
Let's wait three months
and go to Oktoberfest!
All right, baby!
Bring on the beer!
And the scantily clad barmaids!
And the more beer!
Shh!
Hey! I don't smell Bavarian-style vomit.
Where's Oktoberfest?
This is Oktoberfest,
the world's most sophisticated exhibition
of German food, drink, and culture.
Exquisite.
Care for another, sir?
No, I wouldn't want to ruin my Oktoberfest
by becoming intoxicated.
What the hell is going on here?
Fry, quiet.
Oktoberfest is a classy celebration
of how far humans have evolved.
You need to be on your best behavior.
No chance! You can all act
like Jersey Shore socialites,
but at least Bender will party with me.
Right, buddy?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! I enjoy partying
as much as the next fellow,
but this is Oktoberfest. Good day, sir!
Ach du freakin' Lieber!
A sausage contest, eh?
Sounds like fun on a bun!
Shut up! I said it first!
Bam!
Also, ow.
Oh, my God, it's celebrity chef Elzar!
Hey, Elzar, I've just recently started
always having dreamt of being
a sausage-making champion.
Can I get in on this?
Sure, I don't care.
You bring your ingredients?
You bet!
Hold on there, chief. Regular old pork
ain't gonna win this thing.
You gotta get innovative with your meat.
See Chef Fritz over there?
He's only using the choicest cuts
of hummingbird.
Murakami-san got his hands
on a nice rack of angel wings.
Gonna grind 'em up into Heavenwurst.
And me? I'm making my
spice-weaseled bratwurst out of pork.
So you are using pork!
Pork that's been aged for 3,000 years!
Bam!
Aw, man! I can't beat that
with a Craigslist pig.
Sorry, Grundy. I'll have to kill you later
for some other reason.
Sit up straight!
The Countess von Luftballoon is watching.
Ugh!
Man, all the fun has been taken out of
this once-noble barf-a-palooza.
You just say that
because you're primitive.
People in your day
were backwards and crude.
Well, at least we were hammered!
I'm as thirsty as a drunk.
Where do all these child-sized beers
come from?
See that magnificent heavily guarded cask?
All the beer's in there.
Ah!
Not all the beer.
Fahrvergnügen! Kaiser Permanente!
Fruzen Gladje!
Fry! You're embarrassing us!
I don't care! I'm finally having fun!
Hey, come on, you keister-meisters!
Eins, zwei, drei, vier,
lift your Stein and drink your beer!
Ich bin ein never!
Whoa! Even with harps, that's still
the famous Oktoberfest Chicken Dance!
Oh, I almost forgot!
Get das booty up here, Leela!
I brought his and her chicken hats!
Okay, that's it.
You are a boorish, primitive Neanderthal!
Neanderthal?
Yes. And I've had enough!
I'm breaking up with you!
We were going out?
I mean, no!
And keep your stupid chicken hat, too!
And the worst part is,
I had to have the breakup sex by myself!
Fry, some of us have real problems.
I just learned there are people with
fancier sausage meats than me!
I hate future Oktoberfest!
It's supposed to be beer and bratwurst,
not breakups and boring thing!
For hundreds of years,
Oktoberfest has been held here,
in the fertile Neander Valley,
where prehistoric man once hunted
the majestic Schnufel-Ufagus
or woolly mammoth.
To this day, paleontologists
sometimes find entire mammoths
frozen in the valley's icy glaciers,
perfectly preserved
for exactly 30,000 years or so.
Wait a minute,
mammoth meat aged for 30,000 years?
Prize-winning sausage meat, here I come!
I didn't know this ship had
a mammoth detector.
You're drunk, Fry.
This is the elephant detector.
I just set it to "big and woolly."
Mammoth ahoy!
Uh, Bender? I smell burning tusk.
That's probably it. Kill the engine.
Wait till those judges
get their hands on my mammoth sausage!
- My hair is caught! Bender!
- Turn it off!
Sausage is great, sausage is great.
Sausage, sausage, sausage!
This sausage is great!
You, mein Robot,
move on to the next round.
Shut up, Judge, I know it.
Way to go, Bender! Can I try a piece?
You can have yourself a whole big boy.
Mmm. Mmm!
That's good. Where's Fry?
I don't know. Last I saw, he was
jumping up and down in my meat grinder.
By the way, you got a little something
right there.
This is the best sausage I've ever tasted!
Oh, my God! That looks like Fry's hair!
Oh, come on, don't make jokes like that
while I'm eating.
Poor Philip.
He looks so peaceful.
It's tragedy on a bun.
I ate Fry!
I broke up with my boyfriend
and then I ate him!
Oh, now, now. We've all been there.
The pain and guilt are too much!
I can't go on knowing what I've done!
Fry!
Can you really remove
all my memories of Fry?
Oh, they'll still be there, hon.
I'm just gonna snip the links between them
and your conscious brain.
Like this one "Fry falls off zoo train."
He thought he recognized
one of the monkeys!
What was I crying about?
Oh, we were just cuttin' onions, honey.
Let's keep going.
"Fry sits on a pie."
"Fry finds popcorn in his belly button."
"You eat a sausage made of Fry."
"Fry gives you a chicken hat."
Oh, that's sweet.
Good morning!
Geez, who died?
I don't know how Bender and I
do all this work by ourselves.
Maybe we should hire a delivery boy.
You mean like...
Bender! Shh! We have to be careful
not to remind her!
What about my feelings?
Fry was my best friend, and now he's dead!
Nah, I'm just kidding.
My pastor helped me through my grief.
Bender's a jerk, but he's right.
We've all got to accept
that Fry is gone forever.
Whoa. Where happened? What am I?
Sausage is great, sausage is great.
Sausage, sausage, sausage.
Whew! That was close.
Whew!
Ahhh!
Help! Boy trapped in ice!
Oh! Thank you, thank you.
Uh. How you get frozen?
I don't know.
I think I whanged my head pretty bad.
Uh, look normal to me.
The last thing I remember
is losing all my memories.
Who am I, one of you?
Me think so. Anyone dumb enough get
stuck in ice probably Neanderthal.
Neanderthal?
Yeah, I think somebody called me that.
I'm kind of chilly.
I don't suppose you have a...
Oh! Still warm!
So, what's this delivery to McPluto?
Fifty three tons of hamburgers
and French Fragments of not potatoes.
Fragments of not potatoes?
Yep. They get a big shipment
every Fri... Saturday!
What's this?
Oh, it's some kind of
chicken hat! It's cute.
So why does it make me feel,
I don't know, sad?
Why you stare at prehistoric pig butt?
Because it makes me feel happy
and confused and wistful and sad.
- All Neanderthal sad. It in our nature.
- Why?
It all start 30,000 year ago,
in fertile Neander Valley.
Life for our ancestors peaceful,
until Homo sapiens arrive.
We suggest interbreed,
become one big happy species.
But they treat us like
second-class hominid.
They drive us from valley,
and we end up living here,
in isolated crevice.
We figure, "whatever."
But then, we get trapped
by encroaching ice age.
Now we sealed in under sky of ice.
So my sadness makes perfect sense.
And I do have vague memories
of people refusing to breed with me!
A raven's brought word for you, sir.
Guys, guys! My sausage made
the finals at Oktoberfest!
We gotta go back for the closing ceremony!
Oktoberfest?
Sounds like fun!
Chief! Me find huge hole melted in ice,
out past Cesar Chavez ridge!
Hole go all the way outside!
This very interesting.
Maybe someone look into it,
many years from now.
But, Chief, this means
we're not trapped anymore!
It's our chance to take back
the outside world
from those stuck-up Homo sapiens
with their tools and their pants and such.
My fellow big-brows! Are you with me?
You've been staring at that pumpkin
for like, five seconds. What's up?
It's... It's something about the color.
Oh, boo-hoo.
Why are you crying now,
you depressed lunatic?
I don't know. I should be happy.
Bender's sausage just won third place.
Third place?
This is the greatest injustice
Germany has ever committed!
Aha, Leela, we meet again.
But this time,
I'm the one criticizing the sausage.
Dear God, look at those hairy elephantes!
Kill all modern humans!
Hey, this guy's all right.
Battalion A, smash things!
Battalion B, smash different things!
Oh, yeah. Second place!
Release the giant sloth!
- Do something!
- Fear not, Leela.
They may not have technology, like us,
but we have something they don't have.
Technology.
Behold our latest weapon,
a revolutionary fleet of unmanned drones.
With men in them.
Then how are they unmanned?
The men are just for ballast.
I control all the drones
from this single unit.
Foolproof and durable,
it's designed to withstand even the weight
of a modern-day elephant foot.
Chef Fritz, thank God you're all right!
Come with me, I'll protect you!
Neanderthals, load catapult!
Up here in the clouds,
our technology makes us invincible,
like the mighty "X" in tic-tac-toe.
Look at those pathetic cavemen down there,
loading their silly catapult with...
What is that, Kif?
I believe it's a saber-tooth cat, sir.
I guess it's just me and you, chicken hat.
Die, you primitive brute!
What do you Neanderthals want?
We want our land back!
Also, to be treated as equals!
And a little mating wouldn't hurt!
Orange?
Purple?
- Do I know you?
- Have we met?
What Orange-Hair doing with Homo sapien?
Uh, look like interbreeding.
Ow! Ahhh!
You want make love, not war?
Jawohl.
This change everything, Tight-Clothes-Man.
We forgive Homo sapiens
for actions of stuck-up ancestors.
So be it.
In recognition of
your overwhelming victory,
let's call it a draw.
Fry?
Leela?
I didn't recognize you
with your head all swollen.
But it looks better now.
I guess the blood must have rushed
somewhere else.
Guys, guys! Chef Fritz accidentally
got thrown down an icy slope!
I'm the sausage champion!
No further questions!
Rounds for everybody!
Now this is Oktoberfest!
Just like the olden days.
I have to admit, your version is more fun.
They're playing our stupid song!
Care to join me?
No, Leela. Just this once,
I'm going to let you embarrass me.